apexvs.com 2005-12-31

# Apex Learning - Privacy Policy

Apex Learning websites are owned and operated by Apex Learning Inc., a Washington corporation. Please read this Privacy Policy, which tells you what information we collect from users of the Apex Learning websites, how we use that information, and with whom we may share it. Unless defined in this Privacy Policy Conduct, terms capitalized but not defined herein are defined in the  Terms of Use. In this Privacy Policy Apex Learning, Inc. is referred to as " **Apex Learning** ," " **we** ," " **us** ," or " **our** " and you the end user are referred to as " **you** " or " **your** ".

## How Personal Information Is Collected and Updated

 We may collect information that personally identifies you when you register or enroll for an Educational Offering, when you participate in an Educational Offering or when you otherwise communicate with us. We may also obtain your personal information from the institution, such as a school, district, state department of education, or other educational organization funding your participation in Educational Offerings (" **Sponsoring Organization** ").

## Types of Personal Information Collected

 We may collect the following types of personal at the Apex Learning websites:

  1. When students register and/or enroll at any of the Apex Learning websites, we may request the following personal information:

    * Your name and email address
    * Your school name
    * Your school or home school address
    * Your parent or guardian contact information
  2. When students participate in Educational Offering activities your activity scores and your grades will be collected in a password-protected location with limited access by you, your parent(s), your school and personnel from your Sponsoring Organization.
  3. When administrators or teachers register and/or enroll at any of the Apex Learning websites, we may request the following personal information:

    * Your name and email address
    * The names and email addresses of other school contacts
    * Your telephone numbers
  4. If you are paying with a credit card, to process your payment we may also request the following personal information:

    * Your credit card number
    * Your billing information
  5. Teaching tools including standards correlations, lesson plans, and teaching strategies that help teachers easily incorporate Beyond Books into their existing curriculum.

## How Information Is Used and Shared

_Apex Learning Communications_. We may send you communications about updates, services and new Educational Offerings from time to time. If you do not want to receive these communications you can opt out by sending an email to [ support@apexlearning.com](mailto:support@apexlearning.com).

_Grades, Progress & Usage_. We may share with your Sponsoring Organization (or your school) information about grades, progress or usage, including but not limited to, student activity scores, student course grades, student course progress or utilization by students or teachers of the Apex Learning websites.

_Contact Information_. Your contact information may be shared with staff from your school or your Sponsoring Organization. If you enroll in an online course, your name, email address, school, phone number and state of residence will be shared with your online teacher. Your name and email address will be shared with other students in the same section of your online course.

_Processing Payments_. If you are a student or teacher, we may use you name, contact information, and school information to associate you with a purchaser so you can gain access to the relevant offerings at the Apex Learning websites. For credit card purchasers, we provide to the relevant financial institution your credit card number and billing information.

_Legal Requirements_. Apex Learning reserves the right to disclose your personal information as necessary to: (1) comply with the law or comply with legal process served on Apex Learning; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of Apex Learning; (3) protect the personal safety of other Apex Learning websites users or the public; or (4) to ensure compliance with our  Terms of Use or our Student Code of Conduct. Apex Learning cooperates with law enforcement and other third parties to enforce laws, intellectual property, and other rights, and we reserve the right to report any information related to suspicion of illegal activity to law enforcement for prosecution.

## Business Transfers

Information about Apex Learning websites users, including personal information, may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, debt financing, sale of company assets, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personal information could be transferred to third parties as one of the business assets of Apex Learning.

## Third Parties

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose your personal information to third parties. Apex Learning may, however, use for its own purposes, aggregate information that does not identify you personally, or share aggregate information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. For example, we may tell a business partner that x percent of Apex Learning's students are from the West Coast and y percent from the Southern U.S.

## Children and Our Privacy Policy

Apex Learning provides notice of its Privacy Policy to your school and any Sponsoring Organization. Apex Learning relies on the fact that your school's or Sponsoring Organization's authorization for students to enroll and participate in our Educational Offerings is based on the fact that your school has obtained consent from parents to our Privacy Policy.

## Non-personal User Information

An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Internet. When you request pages from Apex Learning websites, our servers log your computer's IP address. Apex Learning collects these IP addresses for the sole purpose of identifying our users' service providers (whether AOL, MSN, etc.) so we can better develop our offerings at the Apex Learning websites. We do not automatically link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, however we can and will use IP addresses to identify users when we feel it is necessary to: (1) comply with the law or comply with legal process served on Apex Learning; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of Apex Learning; (3) protect the personal safety of other Apex Learning websites users or the public; or (4) to ensure compliance with our Terms of Use or our  Student Code of Conduct.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small packet of information that we place on your computer's hard drive whenever you visit the Apex Learning websites. For each user, our web server automatically recognizes the following:

  * the host origin of the request (e.g., your IP address)
  * the referrer (e.g., where you came from if you arrived at our site via a link)
  * the requested document (e.g., the page being viewed)
  * your browser type (e.g., Internet Explorer 5.0)
  * platform information (e.g., Windows 2000, MAC OS 10)
  * session data (e.g., whether login was successful)

Apex Learning uses cookies for a variety of reasons, including without limitation the following:

  * For session variables, to facilitate your navigation of content on the Apex Learning websites.
  * To determine if cookies are enabled in your browser so that we may ensure that our Apex Learning websites run on your computer.
  * To authenticate your access to content on the Apex Learning websites. For example, if you are a student in a calculus course, we use cookies to ensure that you see only calculus course content.

 We do not store in cookies any passwords or credit card information, any information that personally identifies you, or any information that tracks you from session to session.

## Steps You Can Take to Protect Your Privacy

_Links to Other Websites_. You should be aware that when you are on any Apex Learning website, you could be directed to other websites hosted by third parties. We do not endorse those websites. For example, if you "click" a link to a third party site we have listed on one of the pages on the Apex Learning websites, the "click" takes you off the applicable Apex Learning websites. Apex Learning is not responsible for the content or information collection practices of these websites. Please note that these websites may have privacy policies that differ from this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review and understand their privacy practices before providing them with information.

_What You Disclose_. Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online - for example, via message boards, forums, or chats \- that information can be viewed and used by people that you do not know, including but not limited to other students who access at the Apex Learning websites.

_Passwords_. Your access to Educational Offerings is password-protected and only you are authorized to access it and view the information relevant to the account. You agree not to share your passwords with anyone. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords. You agree to sign off from the Apex Learning websites and close your Internet browser window when you have finished accessing and using any Apex Learning website.

_No Guarantee of Security_. No data transmission over the Internet is guaranteed to be secure. Apex Learning does not ensure or warrant the security of any personal or other information you transmit to us including without limitation via the Apex Learning websites.

## Contact Information

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact our support services department at: Apex Learning Inc. 315 Fifth Avenue South, Suite 600, Seattle, WA 98104 or via email at: [ support@apexlearning.com](mailto:support@apexlearning.com). You may also call us toll-free at: 1-800-453-6227.

|
